Crap! There's a frog doing the right crawl!
Come on! After him!
Aye-aye!
Now, what is a lighthouse doing way out here?
I wonder if anyone lives there?
Beep-haw! Beep-haw! Beep-haw!
It's flying! Quick, don't let it get away!
Let's get up ahead of it and block its course!
I guess we ran ashore or something.
What is that sound?
Full reverse right now! Turn 180 degrees!
The Dashing Sea Train and the City of Water!
Water 7!
What the hell is that?
Turn the ship around now!
Hooray!
Grr!
Whoa! That was gross!
The Hulk of Metal is trying to kill us!
Is it a ship?
No way! Something that big and heavy shouldn't even be able to fly!
Hey! What are you doing? Get out of the way!
Oh no! Froggy!
It looked like it was spitting out smoke!
Pirates?
Granny! Granny! Look, we have pirates!
What? Is that true, Timmy?
Okey-dokey, then in that case,
better bring Granny the transponder snail!
It's gonna be a big pain if they call for help when the Marines show up.
What should we do?
Here it is, Granny!
Um, hello?
Who is this?
Sorry, you got the wrong number.
She's totally drunk!
Oh, bye, huh?
That stuff goes good with booze!
Mmm! Yummy!
My name's Chimney!
This is our kitty cat Gombe!
And that's Granny Kokoro!
You fellas wouldn't happen to be train robbers, would ya?
My name's Luffy, and I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Really?
Yep!
I like you, you're funny!
By the way, Chimney, that thing's a steamboat, right?
Seems awfully long to me.
Can't imagine it getting very far.
You've probably never seen anything like this, seeing as it's the only one in the world!
It's not a steamboat, it's a sea train called the Puffing Tom!
How does it work?
It ordered a steam engine to turn its paddle wheels and run on a railway!
Railway?
Uh-huh!
If you look close, you can see the tracks right below the waves!
The train goes the same route every day, taking people from one island to the next!
It carries ships and packages and other stuff, too!
Oh, wow!
Funny we didn't notice it before!
No kidding, we ran right into it!
You should be more careful!
Didn't you see the signal?
There's a bell ringing and everything!
Is that what that thing is for?
I thought it was just here to welcome us!
How are we supposed to know?
And if we couldn't figure it out, then that frog sure wouldn't get it, would he?
It was awful rude of you to hit him like that!
We were gonna catch him and cook him, you know!
Oh!
You saw the frog?
That's Yokozuna!
He sure was an awesome swimmer!
Either way, I wouldn't worry about him, he's pretty tough!
In fact, that wasn't the first time he's challenged the train and lost!
He's really kind of a pain!
If you wanna see him again, just hang around here, I'm sure he'll pop up!
That's why he didn't run!
Wow, I thought that frog was stupid, but it turns out he was just being super manly!
Easy for you to say!
You don't have to put up with him all the time!
I can't even count how many times he's broken the rail cord!
And just imagine what it's like for the passengers when he slams into the train!
That's pretty crazy!
Okay, since that frog's a fighter like me, I'm not gonna eat him after all!
Who would wanna eat that gross thing in the first place?
Anyways, after this, where are you folks headed off to?
The sea train runs to all sorts of places!
There's the town of the Spring Queen, St. Poplar!
There's the gourmet town Pucci, or the carnival town San Faldo!
They're all fun places to go!
And if you happen to work for the government, you can take a special train that's even fancier
than the puffing tom!
The gourmet town Pucci?
Oh, that's the place those people we met on the island were talking about!
Hey, you're right!
Good, then that's the place we're gonna go!
Give it up!
Thanks, but there's no reason for us to take the train when we have our own ship.
We'll just follow the log.
Oh? Where's it pointing to?
Should be someplace east of here.
I see.
Well, in that case, it's Water 7 for sure.
The train you saw on the way here just came from Blue Station on that island.
They call it the City of Water.
I think you'll like it.
Water 7, huh?
They got great shipyards.
You might say that's their claim to fame.
When it comes to boats, they're first class.
They're always coming up with some fancy new technology to build boats for the world government.
Whoa!
Then they must have some awesome shipwrights too!
Some?
More like damn near all of them.
The city's like a regular shipwrights convention!
You hear that?
Yeah!
All right then, it's settled!
We're gonna find the best shipwright in Water 7 and get him to join our crew!
Oh, is that so?
In that case, hold on a sec.
Oopsy-daisy!
You can do it!
Where's she going?
Don't know.
I got a present for you.
This is a little map of the city and a reference letter.
Just give this to a fellow named Iceberg and I promise he'll fix your ship up good.
Water 7's a pretty confusing place.
Be sure not to get lost.
You have a big heart, don't you?
We really owe you one!
We'll be heading back to Water 7 soon, so maybe we'll see you there!
Sounds like a plan to me!
And if you like, I can even give you folks a tour of all my favorite drinking holes!
Sounds good!
We'll try to keep a lookout for you!
It'll take about a week for the log to lock onto the next island, so you'll have plenty of time to do some sightseeing!
Great!
Should be fun!
Okay!
Everyone ready?
Time to set sail!
Yeah!
Thanks again for the map and reference letter!
I sure am glad we ran into you on the way!
Have a safe trip!
Yeah!
Better keep an eye out for all those government types down there!
Yahoo!
Let's go!
City of Meat, here we come!
Did you forget where we're going already?
What a nice wind!
Let's go!
City of Meat, here we come!
Did you forget where we're going already?
What a nice wind.
We might make it out to Water 7 even faster than I thought.
I'll be happy either way.
Don't worry about finding a shipwright.
I got it all under control.
I'll get the hottest girl in town guaranteed.
Who do I care if the shipwright's hot?
I want a huge, manly dude, like even bigger than a bear!
Sixteen feet tall!
A guy that size couldn't even fit on the ship,
and who knows how much food he would have to eat!
All that matters is that he's good at his job.
If you ask me, the real problem's gonna be
finding someone crazy enough to go sailing
with a bunch of pirates.
Size doesn't matter.
I'm just glad we're gonna make a new friend.
We're lucky we ran into that train station on the way.
This map should be a big help.
All we have to do is follow Kokoro's directions
to that iceberg guy and we're set.
I see.
Stupid drunk!
Whoa, looks like Luffy's art.
Okay, let's try to find a shipwright
that looks something like this!
If I saw a guy like that, I'd run!
I wouldn't just run, I'd jump into the sea
to get away from that freak.
He might be part octopus, so even that might not save me.
Don't you have anything better to talk about?
Okay, everybody, since we're gonna be
at Water 7 for a whole week,
let me give you your allowance!
Oh, me first! Me first!
Gimme, gimme!
Please, everyone!
Allowance! Allowance! Allowance! Allowance!
Why are you hugging the ship, Usopp?
I know all these tent plates may not look like much to you,
but they bring back a lot of fond memories for me.
I almost hate to see them go,
but it'll all be worth it if the Mary can finally
get the repairs she needs!
I feel the same way.
I'm proud of her battle scars like anyone else,
but she's taken a real beating
since we've entered the Grand Line.
The deck squeaks and we've got leaks
popping up everywhere.
Nobody wants to admit it,
but if we don't fix this soon,
we're as good as sunk.
Yeah, but even if we can't get a shipwright
for the crew, we still have plenty of money!
We can do more than just fix her!
We can power her up, too!
Ooh! Then let's get more cannons!
Yeah! And a big statue!
Hm. Hey, I think we're there!
Huh?
He's right! I can see Water 7!
All right, men! Time to roll!
The wind's enough.
Don't wear us out before we even get there.
Lovely.
Wow!
Nobody told me it was gonna be this cool!
Whoa!
Check that thing out!
I didn't know they made fountains that big!
Oh! That's nuts!
I've never seen anything like it!
And I thought the sea train was a big deal.
Oh, wow! That's a lot of water!
Do you think it all comes from the ocean?
That's what it seems like.
Then it pours out of the fountain,
goes through the canals,
and falls back into the sea.
Hey! Once we get there,
let's have a race on those water slides!
Water slides?
I think I'll pass!
Even if that was a water slide,
you still can't swim.
Oh, good point.
By the way,
do you have any idea what those numbers mean?
Hmm, good question.
They look like walls,
but they could be some kind of gate.
Duh, those are special entrances
where all the 16-foot shipwrights go in.
How many of those guys
do you think there are out there?
At any rate, that's the station up front.
Must be the same one Kokoro was talking about.
Still, I wonder where the harbor's at.
Inside the town, maybe?
Hey! Hold on!
Pirates shouldn't sail in the front!
You gotta be more discreet!
Use the back street entrance over there instead!
Oh, okay! Thank you!
Whoa!
Look!
There's so many boats!
Awesome!
The city's floating!
Wonder how it works!
But everything's flooded everywhere.
Aren't all the buildings
gonna be full of water too?
Not at all.
The houses here were built
with a submerged foundation in mind.
Hmm?
If you look beneath the walkway,
you'll understand.
You're right!
It's like the city's sitting on stilts!
I see.
Certainly lives up to its name.
Hey!
Hurry up!
Dock the ship!
Whoa!
Hold on a sec!
What do you pirates think
you're doing here in town?
You're not looking to plunder now, are you?
Nuh-uh!
We just wanna get our ship repaired!
You just ask that like it's no big deal?
In that case,
there's a little cape just ahead of here.
Anchor your ship over there for now!
Okay!
Thanks for the help!
They keep waving us off!
Of course they do.
We're flying a pirate flag.
Hmm.
Should be okay to anchor here, right?
Can't see why not.
It's certainly far enough from the city.
Works for me!
For all the sail!
No!
Are you trying to break the ship?
All I did was pull the rope like I always do!
Holy crap!
If the Mary's falling apart this easy, we're lucky we made it here at all!
By the way, they're not scared of pirates here, are they?
Don't you think that's kinda strange?
It's cause we're shipyard customers just like anyone else!
Stop yapping and start fixing the ship already!
They probably aren't concerned about pirates because they have enough security to deal with
them if they misbehave.
Bet there's plenty of marines here, too.
Comes with the territory, huh?
What?
Are you kidding me?!
You...
No!
What are you kidding me?!
You mean they're gonna have us arrested?!
I don't think that'll be a problem since we're paying customers and all.
I guess so.
Well that settles it.
We'll see you later!
Hold on one minute, you two.
Shh!
I need you to come with me to take care of some business.
What business?
First off we're going to take Kokoro's reference letter to this iceberg guy assuming we can find
him.
Hopefully he'll be able to take care of the Miri's repairs for us.
After that, we'll have to find a place where we can trade in our gold for some
where we can trade in our gold for some berries.
Okie dokie, works for me.
So what are we waiting for?
Let's go to Water Survey!
Okay, but aren't you forgetting the gold?
Try to have that mask fixed before we get back, Zoro!
Be careful out there, Nami Sweet!
Hmm, looks like I missed my chance to go with them.
You can go with me later if you like.
Really? Can we go to a bookstore?
Yes, of course.
Maybe we should trade in the gold before anything else.
That's boring. I want to go to the shipyard.
It might not matter to you,
but I'd feel nervous walking around a crowded city
dragging a giant bag of treasure behind me.
If we trade it, we'd still be dragging berries around.
I know, but it'll be a lot smaller, so people won't notice it as much.
I mean, what if we run into thieves?
Ha! We are thieves!
Well, that's true.
But if we cash it in, you won't be the only one carrying the money.
I don't know if I like the sound of that.
It's almost like you don't want me taking care of the gold.
Yep, only you could lose that much gold.
He already forgot it once today.
You guys don't trust me, your own captain?
Nope.
Aw, hey, that really hurts my feelings.
I don't know if I can keep sailing with a crew that...
Wait, what's that?
Huh, that's funny.
Is that the only entrance to the city?
What's a rental bull shop?
Beats me.
Obviously, they must rent out something.
Yeah, but what's a bull?
I don't know.
Like a bulldog?
Oh!
That can't be right.
Excuse me, we'd like to rent some bulls.
Find out what they are first!
Hm?
Hi, looking for some bulls, you said?
How many people?
We've got three.
What kind would you like?
There's three ranks.
Yagada, Rabaka, and King.
And King, for your little group, I'm thinking two Yagadas will do just fine.
Give me one rare and one well done.
You don't know what you're saying, do you?
Oh?
You followed a log to get here?
Yep.
That's quite an achievement, but if you're not from around here,
this is probably the first time you've ever heard about bulls.
Well, to make a long story short, there they are, Yagada bulls.
You can find them all over town.
As you can see, it's a type of fish that swims with its head above the water.
Since the whole city is flooded, we have a lot more canals than walkways.
Because of that, pretty much everyone around here uses the bulls in their daily life.
If you want to go sightseeing, you'll need one too.
So they use the bulls to pull those little boats?
Actually, the boat pot's mounted on their back.
In other words, it's not much different than riding horseback on land.
Huh?
Go ahead and take a look at the bullpen over there if you want to pick one out.
They don't bite.
It'll be 2,000 berries for two two-passenger Yagadas.
Aw, they're cute.
They even look like horses.
That's gross!
What's wrong with you, horsefish?
Ha!
Since that one seems to like you, I'll mount him for you.
Is he all right carrying heavy stuff?
Yeah, these guys are built for power.
The people here use them for moving all the time.
That's a big bag.
Can I ask what's inside?
Gold.
Ha!
That's a good one.
Well, whatever it is, it'll be okay.
See?
Whoa!
Gimme!
Yeah, right!
I guess he thought it was worth asking at least.
This is why I said I don't trust you with the money!
I had to show him.
He didn't believe me.
Wow, I sure wasn't expecting that.
Like I said, that'll be one million berries for two Yagada bulls.
Don't try to change the price on us!
Oops.
I mean five million berries.
It went up even more that time!
Ha, ha, ha!
Can't fool you!
I knew I'd have to watch up for thieves.
Here.
Two thousand berries.
Thank you.
Speaking of gold, do you know where we can get ours cashed in?
Well, there's quite a few places.
But you'd probably clean them all out trying to trade in that much treasure in one shot.
If I were you, I'd check out downtown on the Shipbuilders Island.
We're not really familiar with the area.
Think you could give us some directions?
It's right over there.
Here, take this.
Oh, a map!
Thanks for the help!
Hey, we could find a shipyard downtown too, right?
Yep, best one in the world.
That'll be perfect!
We can head straight to the shipyard soon as we trade in our gold!
Well, you're not going to hear any complaints from me.
As long as the Mary gets repaired, I'll be happy.
Then we'll find a ship ride!
Ha!
Oh man, I can't wait!
Well?
Shall we?
Yeah!
Go Yagada!
See you later!
Thanks for your business and have a safe trip!
Downtown!
Full speed ahead!
Yahoo!
Who doesn't ship!
Who resonates with it?
Who highs temple have a dark blue moon?
There's a book past the room!
Who knows?
He irritates me!
Thoughts only, too, about her and leave view be biod!
Grand郎 bike to my mind!
You have to worry to 0!
Yeah!
DOOitted!
God!"
Mohammad
Next, One Piece! Adventure in the city on the water!
Head to the Mammoth Shipbuilding Plant!
I'm gonna be king of the pirate!